Kaufman, Jacob J. Papers 6190
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Publications on Railroads and Kaufman's ILR Courses and Research., Publication (Box 3)
  - Arbitration Syllabus: ILR 602, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Economics of Wages and Employment: ILR 240.01, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Spring Semester
  - Labor Law Course Outlines, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Collective Bargaining Checklist, Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Cost-Effectiveness in Education Research Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Handwritten Notes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Long Island Railroad, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Labor Relations Update, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Author: Labor Relations Department
      Notes: v.1:Special Edition (1986:Sep.)
    - Item 2: Labor Relations Update, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Notes: v.1:Special Edition (1986:Sep.). Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Labor Relations Update, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Notes: v.1:Special Edition (1986:Sep.). Copy 3.
  - Railroad Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Railroad Worker Education, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Includes 4 photographs
  - Relationship Between Education and Learning, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Research Activities, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UTU Agreement with the National Carriers' Conference Committee, 1982; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: UTU Agreement with the National Carriers' Conference Committee, 1982; Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Author: United Transportation Union (UTU); National Carriers' Conference Committee
      Notes: October 15, 1982.
  - UTU Agreement with the Rochester and Southern Railroad, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: UTU Agreement with the Rochester and Southern Railroad, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Author: United Transportation Union (UTU); Rochester and Southern Railroad
      Notes: April 22, 1986.
  - Union Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - United Steelworkers of America Testiment for Jacob Kaufman, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Jacob Kaufman Testimony, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jacob J. Kaufman: Vita, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)